Lonely at the top, eh?
They're moving us tomorrow.
Maybe I can get you out of here.
And we can make the
whole world our bitch.
We need a secret code.
No, that's stupid, Russell.
Idiot.
We're a team.
We're like thugs,
we're like gangsters.
I'm like Tupac, and
you're like Ice Cube.
Supposedly, she can rap, too.
Yeah.
I like that.
Terrific, these
are all terrific.
Meet Bedlam.
Cool name! Superpowers?
I can distort electrical fields.
Including the one
inside your brain...
causing anxiety, confusion...
pain.
So, basically, you're
Dave Matthews.
We can use him.
I'm Zeitgeist.
Cool. I like it.
So you have the power
to put your finger on
the pulse of society?
No.
No, I spit acidic vomit.
Oh.Do you want me
to demonstrate? DEADPOOL: No!
We'll take your word for it.
Thank you. Yeah. Listen, we've
all eaten at Arby's, okay?
And this is the Vanisher.
But...
Vanisher!
Nice! Right?
He's not here, is he?
He may be running late.
My name's Rusty, but
I go by Shatterstar.
That's good, yeah.
"Rusty" is terrible.Toughie.
So, uh, where are you from?
The planet Mojo World.
So you're an alien, I guess.
Bad name.
How does that, uh, help us?
I'm basically better
than you at everything.
Just once, I'm gonna
find a planet of people
that are worse than
me at everything.
A whole bunch of
functional idiots.
I'm gonna go there, and I'm
gonna be their Superman.
Isn't that Canada?
You shut your goddamn
trash mouth!
Meet... Domino.
What's your shtick? I'm lucky.
That's not a superpower.
Yeah, it is. No, it isn't.
Yes, it is. No, it isn't.
Yeah, it is. Really isn't.
No, it isn't.Yes, it is.
Told you.
Get out of my head!
I'm not in your head.
I'm in an 11-year-old's bedroom.
Well, if you're so lucky,
then what are you
doing here with us?
I don't know yet.
What's that supposed to mean?
There's a reason why I'm here,
and I'll know when I know.
Everything usually just
kind of works out for me.
Like 2008 Ryan Reynolds.
I don't know who that is.
You're hired.
Lucky me.
I like her!
And last, but not least...
Peter.
Am I getting catfished
here or...?
Any powers you wanna
tell us about?
No.
I don't have one.
Um, I just saw the ad.
No superpowers at all?
Uh, I have both Type
1 and 2 Diabetes.
Ow! Oh!
That's all the diabetes.
Right? Yeah, you got 'em all.
If you find a Type
3, let us know.
Yeah.
You're in.
Yeah. Fuck!
It's fulfilling work.
Let's go!
This is Convoy 17
departing the Ice Box.
We are en route.
Peacetime makes people soft.
I was born into war.
Bred into it.
Okay.
What's the most pain
you've ever felt?
These restraints are pretty...
People think they
understand pain.
They have no concept of it
beyond their own
worst experience.
5 years old. That's what?
A bee sting.
Oh, yeah.
20 years old, shrapnel.
40 years old, disease.
Maybe the kind that leaves
you more machine than man.
Yeah, getting old's
not for sissies.
That's what my Grandma
Ginny used to...
I've got a list.
We're gonna work down it.
Together.
Number one, I'm gonna
bend something.
Something that was
not meant to bend.
I'm gonna stop you right there
because I'm not gonna
make it to two.
I won't even make it to one.
I don't do well with
pain, you know.
If I stub my toe, I'm
done for the day.
I cried when they
canceled Felicity.
When I get really scared,
I get nervous erections.
I have one right now.
Don't look. It'll
only make it worse.
I don't want you to hurt me,
and I'll tell you
anything you wanna know.
Except for where they are.
Russell's in a convoy
heading southbound
on Gerry Duggan Parkway.
The monster's with them. I
wouldn't fuck with him.
You all know the plan.
Intercept the convoy,
grab the boy. But not
inappropriately!
You know what,
I wouldn't fuck with
Deadpool either.
Because he's built a team.
He's unstoppable.
He has an ass pen. He'll
stab you with it.
Watch out for this guy, Cable!
He's very short, 5'11".
Not like in the comics.
And if we succeed, we
all go home early.
So if you go after them,
Cable, I warn you...
there's a wind
advisory in effect.
A little turbulent up here.
I don't know much about
this Cable fella...
but I guarantee he hasn't killed
as many people as melanoma has.
We're getting close!
As a former X-Man...
Trainee. Thank you, Bedlam.
I was always appalled
by the blatant sexism
in the group's name.
X-Men! Men!
The point is, our group
will be forward thinking.
Gender neutral.
From now on, we'll
be known as...
X-Force.
Isn't that a little derivative?
I don't recall asking
your opinion, Peter!
That wasn't me.
Hang the laundry out
at 1,300 feet...
intercept the convoy,
and grab the boy.
Let's bring on the
carnage, baby!
Get me on the ground,
watch me go!
Yeah!
I can't wait to kill!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
I just wanna say how
proud I am of this team.
You know, you guys look amazing!
Vanisher, I have no doubt
you look amazing too.
This is the family
that I've always dreamed
of having and I...
Ah, shit.
I just get a little
choked up sometimes.
I hate to interrupt,
but is anybody nervous
about the high winds?
Gary. My name's Peter.
I realize that you're
new to this, but relax.
You've been chosen
by a higher power.
Did he just call himself God?
I think he did.
I'd like to go home.
And I'd like...
the McRib to be
available year round,
but sometimes dreams
don't come true.
I spent 10 years
in Special Forces.
You think we didn't
jump out of the plane
because of a light breeze?
You're in this shit
now, Mustache!
I'm only yelling to
impress the other guys.
I'd never let anything
happen to you, Sugarbear.
Leonard, hit it!
Go! Go! Go!
Let's get some!
Whoo!
Oh, yeah!
Convoy, 12 o'clock!
On my command!
Deploy! Oh, hey now!
Whoa!
Little off course here.
Holy mommy fucking shit!
Ah, there they are.
Look at these gorgeous
sons of bitches.
Oh, yeah! That's right, Bedlam!
No! Tripping
motherfucking billies!
Shatterstar. Okay, you got this.
Left!
You'd have to be insane
to take off in this.
No, stage left, you idiot!
Well, I guess we found something
you're not better at.
Vanisher.
Maybe the wind can't
blow what it can't see.
Oh! Really?
All right, we could
do this with four.
Sugarbear. You got this, buddy!
That's the stuff! That's
the X-Force spirit!
Never underestimate a
man with a mustache!
Just ask anyone in Brooklyn.
We did it!
You're a goddamn superhero, you!
X-Force!
X-Force.
Oh!
Peter.
I got you, buddy!
You're gonna be fine!
This is not good, man!
You got this, big guy!
Here we go, Peter!
Look at me. We're
X-Force, right?
Yeah, we're X-Force.
We're X-Force.
Oh, my God! What the fuck?
Fucking acidic vomit!
Oh, God! I'm gonna
throw up in my mask.
Okay, I'm over the convoy.
Where did the rest
of the team land?
Good news and bad news.
Bad news is the
whole team is dead.
The good news is,
I don't think anyone's
gonna miss Shatterstar.
He was a bit of a prick.
Oh, but Paul!
Peter!
Peter, I'm gonna miss him most.
But there is a slight chance
Vanisher could make it.
Nope, no chance. He's dead.
The whole team?
Only the main ones.
We're still good.
Fuck, you are dumb.
Whoever planned this stunt's
been smoking a lot jazz cabbage.
I'll tell you that much.